時は戦国、乱世の時代。
からくり人の住むジパング国では群雄割拠して合戦に明け暮れ、
からくり武芸者たちも勝利と栄光を目指してしのぎを削っていた。
そしていま、からくり武芸者ナンバー１を目指す、とてつもないヒーローが誕生した！
ムサシ、見参でござるだス！
からくり剣豪伝ムサシロード
男はいつでも　世界の真ん中で
いちばん　強くなる日を
AH! AH! 夢見て
心の刃　大空にふりかざし
冒険の旅の　幕を開ける
ジパング国を　さすらう剣豪
その名　からくりびと　ムサシ
GO! FIGHT!
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　昨日よりも　今日　強い
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
明日は　輝くぞ
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　思い切りと　静けさと
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
みけんが　きらめいた　ムサシ！！
슈텐타이거는 사금을 얻기 위해 마을 사람들을 강제로 부리고 있었다.
Shutentiger was forcing the villagers to work to mine gold sand.
무사시, 코지로는 산타의 부탁을 들어 격심한 전투 끝에 슈텐타이거를 대폭발시켰다.
Musashi and Kojirō responded to Santa's wish, and after an intense fight, they made Shutentiger explode.
히익!
이시마츠의 유령이오
Woah!
It's Ishimatsu's Ghost!
여행을 계속하던 일행은 노독을 풀기 위해 온천에 들렀다.
Our heroes have stopped by at a hot spring to relieve their strain from all that journey.
뭐가 어쨌더라도 온천이 제일이구나.
Hot springs are great as always.
저기, 코지로, 우리도 온천에 들어가오.
Hey, Kojirō, let's get into the hot spring too-dasu.
센히메 님이 습격당하면 어쩔 셈이냐? 그런 태평한 일할 틈이 있을 것 같냐!
What if Senhime gets attacked? Do you think we have time to enjoy something at leisure?
흠, 그럼 나, 오센짱하고 같이 탕에 들어가서 망보겠소.
Hmm, then I'll join Osenchan in the bath and stand watch-dasu.
바, 바보야! 너, 예의도 모르냐!
You idiot! Don't you know your etiquette?
해야 할 일을 할 뿐이오.
I'm just doing what I have to-dasu.
그럼!
Then!
말했잖아.
Told you so.
이렇게 강하면 지킬 필요 없소...
With that strength of hers, do we even have to protect her-dasu...?
무사시!
Musashi!
왠지 기분 나쁜 여관이오.
This is one eerie inn-dasu.
뭐냐, 무사시. 무섭냐?
What is it, Musashi? Are you scared?
그, 그런 건 아니오!
T- that's not it-dasu!
그래도 무릎을 떨고 있잖아.
But aren't you shivering your knees?
이, 이, 이건 저녁이 늦어서 다리를 떨고 있는 것이오.
I- I'm just shaking my legs because the dinner is late-dasu.
공주님, 조심하세요!
Princess, watch out!
식사 가져왔습니다.
Dinner is ready.
뭣이오, 단지 여관 주인이었소! 놀래키지 않았으면 좋겠소!
Oh, it was just the inn owner-dasu! Please don't scare us like that-dasu!
무사시 정말 겁쟁이구나.
You sure are a scaredy cat, Musashi.
아, 아니오. 방금 그건 우와, 겨우 요리가 나왔다! 이었을 뿐이오.
N- no, that isn't it-dasu. I was just like, "Wow, the food is finally here!"-dasu!
아, 정말 배고팠소! 잔뜩 먹겠...소...
I was so hungry-dasu! I'll eat as much as... I... wanted-dasu...
이것밖에 없소?
Is this all you have-dasu?
다이어트 메뉴도 이것보다는 많을 거야.
Even a diet menu would have more than this.
이건 좀 지나치지 않아?
Isn't this too small of a portion?
미안합니다. 그렇지만 이게 드릴 수 있는 최고의 요리입니다.
I'm sorry. But this is the best meal we can offer.
뭔가 사정이 있는 것 같군. 괜찮으시다면 말씀해주시지 않겠습니까.
It seems that he has something to tell. Would you like to share your story with us?
예. 사실은 이 마을 가까이에 오소레잔이라는 영혼이 모이는 산이 있습니다.
Yes. There is a mountain named Osorezan near this village, and it is told that spirits gather in there.
그 곳에 최근 목이 없는 패잔 무사의 망령이 나타나 날뛰었습니다.
Recently at there, the departed spirits of fleeing soldiers have appeared and raged.
아주 겁에 질린 마을 사람들은 이곳저곳 마을을 떠나, 남아 있는 건 이 여관 하나뿐입니다.
The villagers got scared and left the village, and this inn is the only one to remain here.
아주 못된 유령이네. 용서할 수 없어. 좋아, 그 유령을 퇴치해 주겠어.
Those are really bad ghosts. Alright, we will get rid of those ghosts.
정말입니까?
Really?
자자잠깐, 오센짱, 그건 어떻게 봐도 위험하오!
J- j- just a moment, Osenchan! That's too dangerous-dasu!
어라, 내가 한다고는 한 적 없어. 네가 퇴치할 거야, 네가.
Hey, I never said that I'm going to do that myself. It's you who's going to wipe them out. You will.
어... 나이오?
Uh... I will-dasu?
-무섭니?
-에이, 설마이오.
-Are you scared?
-Err, no way-dasu.
그렇지! 무사시는 훌륭한 무예가지!
That's right! Musashi is an excellent martial artist!
알았다면 됐소.
It's good if you know that-dasu.
그 유령, 눈도 목도 아무것도 없는 주제에 이렇게 나타나.
Those ghosts do not have an eye, a neck, or anything, and will appear like this...
거 무사시도 참, 이런 이야기에 약하다니까.
You sure are a chicken, Musashi.
오센짱, 밥은 이제 됐으니까 빨리 자오.
Osenchan, I don't care about dinner anymore, so please, let's just sleep now-dasu...
싫어. 겨우 유령을 볼 수 있는 기회인데. 안 보고 잘 수 있을 것 같니?
No way! This is a rare chance to see ghosts with my bare eyes. Do you think I can sleep without seeing one myself?
그렇지, 코지로?
Don't you agree, Kojirō?
코지로? 넌 무섭지 않아?
Kojirō, aren't you scared?
예. 저는 마침 유령이란 걸 믿지 않아서요.
Yes. Coincidentally, I don't believe in ghosts at the moment.
그럼 유령을 퇴치하시오.
Then you go take ghosts down-dasu.
나는 센히메 님을 호위하는 게 사명. 그 이상도 이하도 아니다.
My duty is to protect Senhime. Nothing more or less than that.
역시 코지로도 겁에 질렸소.
I see that you're scared too, Kojirō-dasu.
이런 때는 분명 유령이 나올 것입니다. 그럼 저는...
This means that ghosts will show up soon. Then...
-그럼 이만.
-아, 주인!
-Night!
-Hey, mister!
재밌어졌네.
It just became interesting.
어째서이오...
How-dasu...
가자, 무사시, 코지로!
Go, Musashi, Kojirō!
아, 그 전에 잠깐 화장실에 갔다 오겠소!
F- First, let me go to toilet-dasu!
무사시!
Musashi!
무사시...
Musashi...
이게 무서워지니까 오줌이 매려져서 안 되겠소.
I gotta stop wanting to go pee when it gets scary-dasu...
무사시...
Musashi...
누, 누, 누구이오!
W- w- who's there-dasu?!
어라, 왜 이런 곳에 단고... 코지로 놈도 참, 가끔은 소원도 들어주오!
Hey, why are dangos here? I guess Kojirō does understand what I wish for-dasu!
먹을 게 있으면 고분고분히 말하면 될 것이오.
If he's with something to eat, he should have just told me-dasu.
잘 먹겠소!
Thank you for this!
어, 어라?
H- huh?
어라, 못 본 새에 저기까지 갔소.
Huh, it moved that far while I wasn't looking at-dasu.
어라? 어이, 멈추시오! 거 참 활기찬 단고오!
Huh? Hey, stop-dasu! You're one lively dango-dasu!
정말, 무사시도 참. 진짜로 무서워서 도망쳤나 봐.
I knew it. Musashi ran away because he was scared.
어, 무사시!
Hey, Musashi!
어이, 무사시!
어이, 멈추시오!
Hey, wait-dasu!
저 자식 참 근성 없는 놈이야.
He has no courage whatsoever.
아니요, 뭔가 모습이 이상합니다.
No, something looks very wrong with him.
-어?
-따라갑시다.
-Huh?
-Let's follow him.
거 참, 단고쨩 어디로 숨었소...
I wonder where did that dango-chan hide to-dasu...
어이, 무사시! 오랜만이다!
Hey, Musashi! Long time no see!
이, 이시마츠 씨!
I- Ishimatsu!
이시마츠는 무사시에게 형과 같은 존재였다.
Ishimatsu was like an older brother for Musashi.
어이!
Heya!
그, 그래도, 이시마츠 씨는 죽었을 텐데...
B- but, Ishimatsu, you were supposed to be dead.
뭐, 보는 대로 내가 유령이지.
Yeah, just as you see, I'm a ghost.
오랜만에 만났는데 좀 차갑지 않냐, 형제?
It's been a long time, and this is how you treat me, bro?
이시마츠 씨, 살아 있을 때부터 방향치였으니...
Ishimatsu, you never had a sense of direction even when you were alive...
역시 길을 잃어서 성불 못한 것이오?
Did you get lost again and couldn't rest in peace-dasu?
이 자슥! 저 세상에 가는 길이라는 건 길을 잘못 찾을 수조차 없는 외길이야!
You idiot! The road to the other world cannot be any more straight!
그래도 말야, 그 길을 나 혼자서 걸어가는 건 왠지 외로워서 말야.
But, you know, walking that path alone is somewhat lonely.
무사시, 나하고 같이 가지 않을래?
Musashi, wouldn't you like to go with me?
어? 나보고 죽으란 것이오?
Huh? Are you telling me to die-dasu?
그렇지!
Right!
그, 그건 아무리 이시마츠 씨의 부탁이라 해도 들어줄 수 없소.
I- I can't accept that wish even for you-dasu, Ishimatsu.
그 때 먹은 형제의 단고는 맛있었지...
The dangos of brotherhood that we had back then was great...
그렇소!
You're right-dasu!
그 때, 니가 그 짓거리 안 했으면 난 안 죽고 살아 있었겠지.
If you didn't mess up back then, I would be living instead of being dead.
그 때는 정말 미안했소.
I am really sorry about what happened back then-dasu.
그래도 말야, 지금은 다 좋은 추억이야!
But you know, it's all good memories now!
어떠냐, 무사시! 다시 그 때처럼 둘이서 즐겁게 여행할 생각 없냐!
How's this, Musashi? Wouldn't you like to travel by two with me like how we did back then?
그, 그래도! 나, 죽는 건 역시 무섭소.
B- but! Dying is still scary-dasu...
거 참 패기도 없는 놈이군. 그럼 나하고 같이 죽으면 불만 없겠지?
How spiritless are you? I guess you'd be satisfied if we die together?
그렇소! 그렇게 하면 딱 좋소!
That's it-dasu! That will work perfectly-dasu!
좋아! 그럼 서두르자!
Alright! Then let's hurry!
그럼 내가 수를 셀 테니까, 하나, 둘, 셋 하면 뛰어내리자!
I'll count; let's jump off when I say one, two, and three!
알겠소!
Got it-dasu!
그럼 가자! 하나...
Then let's do this! One...
둘에...
Two and...
-셋!
아니!
-Three!
-Errr-
괜찮소, 이시마츠 씨?
Are you okay, Ishimatsu?
아, 나, 나는 신경쓰지 마라! 바로 뛰어내렸으면 좋았을 텐데.
Erm, f- forget about me! It could have been better if you jumped down right away.
아니아니, 더는 이시마츠 씨를 혼자 있도록 냅둘 수는 없소!
No, I can't let Ishimatsu be alone and be lonely-dasu!
성가신 놈이구나.
Aren't you cumbersome...
좋아! 마음을 다잡고 다시 한번 가자!
Alright! Let's brace ourselves up and try this again!
하나!
One!
둘에!
Two and...
셋!
Three!
어라? 이시마츠 씨 왜 안 뛰어내리오?
Huh? Ishimatsu, why aren't you jumping off-dasu?
아, 아니, 그건 말야...
U- uh, I can explain...
나, 이시마츠 씨에게 질문이 있소.
I have a question for you-dasu, Ishimatsu.
뭐냐?
What is it?
유령이라는 건 두 번도 죽을 수 있소?
Can a ghost die twice-dasu?
이, 이 자슥! 귀여운 아우인 너를 위해서라면 난 몇 번이라도 죽을 수 있어!
I- idiot! For my cute younger brother, I can die again, over and over!
그런 것이었소! 그렇게나 날 생각해줬던 것이오!
That was it-dasu! You thought about me that much-dasu!
어이, 위험하잖아!
Hey, watch out!
무사시, 잡소리는 생각하지 말고 서둘러 뛰어내리자!
Musashi, nevermind about whatever; let's just jump off!
-무사시!
-Musashi!
그렇소! 저 둘한테 작별의 인사를 해야 하오!
Oh, right. I must bid farewell to those two-dasu!
에잇, 어서 죽어라!
Damn! Just die already!
뭐야? 누구냐!
What the-?! Who's there?!
무사시!
Musashi!
방해꾼이군!
Meddlers, I see!
-무사시!
-있으면 있다고 답을 해!
-Musashi!
-Say something if you're there!
나 여기 있소! 어이!
I'm here-dasu! Hey!
-무사시!
-너 대체 뭐하냐?
-Musashi!
-What in the world are you doing?
너 정말 바보구나. 대체 세상에 유령에게 꾀여서 쉽게 죽자고 하는 사람이 있냐!
Are you an idiot or what? Who else in the world would be lured by a ghost and get asked to die together?
그래도, 나, 끈끈한 인연을 맺은 이시마츠 씨의 부탁은 거절할 수 없소.
But I cannot refuse Ishimatsu's favor, especially when we formed a firm bond-dasu...
그 이시마츠의 유령, 이상하지 않니?
That Ishimatsu's ghost... Isn't something weird?
이상하오?
Weird?
너, 걷어차였다고 했지? 유령이 그런 짓을 하냐?
You said you got kicked off. Can a ghost even do that?
그건 그렇지만...
That's true-dasu, but...
게다가 널 구한 줄은 대체 누가 던졌어?
Moreover, who threw the rope that saved your life?
그러게...
Dunno...
내 예감으로는 그 답은 전부 오소레잔에 있을 것 같다.
According to my hunch, all the answer should be at that Osorezan.
오소레잔에 숨겨진 비밀은 무엇인가? 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
What kind of secret is hidden in that Osorezan? Wait for the stormy latter half!
와, 뜨뜻미지근한 바람이 부는 게 분명 뭐가 나올 것 같은 분위기야.
Wow. This lukewarm wind... It feels like something's about to show up.
아니, 이건 대체...
What's going on?
코지로! 오센짱! 어디이오!
Kojirō! Osenchan! Where are you-dasu?!
난 여기 있어!
I'm over here!
-센히메 님!
-나도 여기 있어!
-Senhime!
-I'm here too!
응?
Huh?
센히메 님! 무사시! 여긴 안개가 갤 때까지 움직이지 않는 게 좋아요.
Senhime! Musashi! You'd better not move here until the fog clears up.
-일단 기다립시다!
-그래!
-Let's wait for now!
-Got it!
알겠소!
Roger-dasu!
어? 코지로이오?
Huh? Is it Kojirō?
-어이, 무사시.
-이시마츠 씨!
-Hey, Musashi.
-Ishimatsu!
무사시, 어제는 실패했지만 오늘은 사이좋게 저 세상에 가자!
Musashi! Though we've failed yesterday, we'll go to the other world today as friends!
저, 그게... 나는 역시 죽는 건 싫소.
You know... I don't want to die-dasu.
그 때 먹은 단고는 맛있었지...
The dangos that we had back then was great...
맛있었소!
It was great-dasu!
그 때하고 똑같이, 나는 그 감동을 너하고 나누고 싶어.
Just like how we did back then, I'd love to share the impression with you.
이시마츠 씨, 정말 다정한 분이오!
Ishimatsu! You're so kind-dasu!
자, 무사시! 이번엔 틀림없이 죽을 수 있을 거야.
Musashi! We will make it to death this time.
그, 그렇소.
Y- you're right-dasu.
자, 오늘은 똑바로 가자!
Let's do this properly today!
알겠소.
Got it-dasu.
일단 그 전에...
Before that...
뭐, 뭔 짓이냐.
W- what are you doing?
이렇게 하면 실패할 일 없이 같이 뛰어내릴 수 있소.
With this, we will be able to jump down together without any mistakes-dasu.
뭐?!
What?!
자, 이제 가오.
Let's go-dasu.
그, 그게, 무사시, 나, 이렇게 묶여 있는 건 별로 좋아하지 않아.
Uh, that is... M- Musashi, I... I don't like being tied like this; it looks uncool.
관두자.
Let's not.
죽을 거라면 좋고 싫고 관계 없소!
If you're gonna die, looking uncool doesn't matter-dasu!
가오!
Let's go-dasu!
이, 있잖아, 조금만 묶어서 스을쩍 손이 빠지게 하지 않을래?
Y- you know, can't you just tie it lightly so that I can pull my hand out?
안 되오.
No way-dasu.
그, 그럼, 좀만 사알짝 떨어질 수 있도록 좀 안심되는 곳에서 떨어지지 않을래?
T- then, wouldn't you like to fall from somewhere more relaxing that we can fall more softly?
그러면 못 죽소!
Then we can't die!
이제 적당히 포기하고 단념하시오!
That's enough; give it up-dasu!
머, 멍청아! 그만해!
I- idiot! Stop it!
이, 이 꼬맹이가!
Y- you pipsqueak!
뭐, 뭔 짓이오, 이시마츠 씨!
W- what are you doing-dasu, Ishimatsu?!
괜찮냐, 무사시!
Are you okay, Musashi?!
어?
Huh?
네 이놈!
Curse you!
어, 이시마츠 씨!
Hey, Ishimatsu!
무사시, 이 멍청한 새꺄! 저 놈은 유령이 아니랬지!
Musashi, you dimwit! I told you that he's not a ghost!
그래도! 저런 이시마츠 씨를 그냥 두고 볼 수는 없소!
But I can't leave Mr. Ishimatsu like that-dasu!
저 이시마츠가 유령이라면, 너희 우정은 수상하구나.
If that's the ghost of Ishimatsu, then your so-called friendship is fishy.
정말 이시마츠가 죽지 못했다면, 무사시, 네 힘으로 성불시켜 줘라!
If Ishimatsu really couldn't rest in peace, then you should bring him to peace!
그게 죽은 친구에게의 참된 우정 아니냐!
Wouldn't that be the correct deed for your departed friend?
아, 그렇소.
Yes, you're right-dasu.
센히메 님, 계속 신경쓰이는 게 있는데, 이 오소레잔은 사람들을 불러들이고 있는 것 같습니다.
Senhime, this has been bothering me; this Osorezan seems to be calling people towards it.
오센짱!
Osenchan!
살려줘!
Help me!
이시마츠 씨!
Ishimatsu!
무사시! 이번엔 방해받지 않게 동료를 데려왔다! 자, 다 함께 같이 삼도천을 건너자!
Musashi! I brought your comrades, so that there won't be any more meddlers! Now, let us cross Sanzu River all together!
(lit. river of three crossings. The Styx)
뭐야, 이거! 관둬! 그만해!
What's this?! Let me go! Let me go!
이시마츠 씨! 외로운 건 알겠는데 삼도내는 혼자서 건너길 바라오.
Ishimatsu! I get that you're lonely, but I want you to cross the Sanzu by yourself-dasu.
그 때 먹은 단고는 맛있었지...
The dangos that we had back then was great...
-그랬었소!
-무사시!
-That's right-dasu!
-Musashi!
넌 내 말이나 들으면 된다!
You'd better listen to me!
뭐야? 너, 그 때 단고가실은 맛없었던 거냐!
What's this? Were the dangos we had back then not good enough?!
맛있었지만 그것보다도 더 맛있는 펀치를 내가 주겠소!
It was great, but I will offer you a more delicious punch-dasu!
이시마츠 씨는 내가 성불해 주겠소!
I will have you rest in peace with my hands-dasu, Ishimatsu!
그건 고맙다!
Well, thank you!
이시마츠 씨, 언제 이런 기술을 배웠소?
Ishimatsu, when did you learn techniques like this-dasu?!
저 세상에서 배웠지.
From the other world.
코지로!
Kojirō!
죽어라, 무사시!
Die, Musashi!
누, 누구냐!
W- who is it?!
무사시 님. 속으면 안 됩니다.
Musashi, you must not be fooled.
이 자는 이시마츠가 아닙니다.
This guy is not Ishimatsu.
주베 씨!
Jūbee!
무사시 님. 이 녀석의 정체를 똑똑히 봐 두십시오!
Musashi, see for yourself! The true identity of that man!
넌 오니히메!
You are Onihime!
네 이놈, 주베! 눈 앞이었는데 잘도 방해했겠다!
Jūbee, you rat! It was so close and you had to get in the way!
기억해 둬라!
Remember this!
주베 님. 어째서 여기에?
Jūbee. What brought you here?
그 이야기는 나중에. 일단 서둘러 오니히메를 쫓읍시다.
We'll talk about that later. For now, we must chase Onihime.
역시 그랬군.
I knew it.
주베 씨, 뭐가 역시이오?
Jūbee, what did you know-dasu?
사실은 얼마 전, 제너럴 이에야스 님이 원인 불명의 고열로 쓰러졌습니다.
To tell you the truth, not too long ago, General Ieyasu has broken down because of a high fever of unknown reason.
어? 할아버지가?
What? My grandpa?
의사들이 얼마고 알아보아도 원인을 알 수 없었습니다. 그래서 기도사에게 점을 치도록 했더니,
Doctors couldn't find out the reason. That's why we asked a shaman for a purification,
북쪽에서 이에야스 님에게 저주를 거는 영파가 발생하고 있다는 결과가 나왔습니다.
and we found that there is a spiritual wave from the north side that is cursing General Ieyasu.
그게 저것이란 소리오.
You're saying that it's that-dasu, right?
틀림없이.
No doubt about it.
그럼 마을에서의 유령 소란도 역시...?
Then the disturbance in the village too?
이 장소에 대해 알아보니, 전부 오니히메가 건 요술이었습니다.
When I investigated this place, everything was under Onihime's sorcery.
오니히메?
Onihime?
너희들, 이젠 살살 할 필요가 없다. 오소레잔의 모든 영파를 제너럴 이에야스에게 보내라.
The time has come for you to not hold back. Send all the spiritual wave from Osorezan to General Ieyasu.
천하를 우리에게!
The world will be ours!
인간의 마음을 가지고 노는 것도, 제너럴 이에야스에게까지 손을 뻗치는 건 용서할 수 없소!
Not only playing with the minds of people, but also trying to meddle with General Ieyasu is unforgivable-dasu!
주베 씨, 코지로! 저 주술, 어떻게든 조치해 주겠소!
Jūbee and Kojirō! We will deal with that sorcery-dasu!
힘내, 모두!
Do your best, everyone!
오니히메! 네놈의 악행은 내가 용서하지 않겠소!
Onihime! I will not forgive for what you did to me-dasu!
방해는 소용없다!
You may not interfere!
무엇보다도 내 소중한 추억을 가지고 놀았겠소!
Most of all, you dared to play with my precious memories-dasu!
흥, 그런 걸 소중하게 여긴 네 잘못이다.
Hmph, it's your fault for even treating those preciously.
용서할 수 없소!
I will not forgive you-dasu!
너희들, 한방에 이 녀석들을 쫒아버려라!
Everyone! Take care of all of them at once!
이런 건방진!
How impudent!
주베 씨!
Jūbee!
젠장, 그 쪽이 회오리라면 이 쪽에서도 회오리로 승부이오!
If you're going with a whirlwind, then I'm going with a whirlwind, too-dasu!
이천일류, 회오리검!
Niten'ichiryū: Tatsumakiken!
(lit. Tornado Sword)
훌륭합니다, 무사시 님!
That was excellent, Musashi!
네 이놈!
You bastard!
오니히메!
Onihime!
포기해라, 오니히메! 악행을 찬양했던 선례는 없다!
Give it up, Onihime! There is no precedent of praising the evil!
에이, 닥쳐라!
Shut up!
아름다운 얼굴을 숨기고서 뭘 위해 이런 악행을 하나.
Hiding your beautiful face, why are you doing these evil deeds?
흥, 넌 내 기분을 절대 알지 못할 테다!
Hmph! You will never understand what's in my mind!
기억해 둬라. 이 복수는 꼭 하겠다!
Remember this. I will pay this back!
도망치지 마시오, 오니히메!
Do not run away, Onihime!
멈춰라, 무사시!
Stop, Musashi!
뭣이오?
What?
어?
Hm?
그럼 저는 여기까지. 센히메 님도 어느 쪽도 조심하세요.
Then I'll be going now. Senhime and both of you, be careful.
고마워, 주베. 자, 무사시. 도중에 무서운 이야기 잔뜩 해 줄게.
Thank you, Jūbee. Musashi, let me tell you all the scary stories during our way.
그건 하지 말아 주시오!
Please don't do that-dasu!
낮이라면 무섭지 않잖아?
It isn't scary when it's bright, you know!
-아니, 그런 문제가 아니오!
-저기, 무사시! 이 주변에 있는 무덤에...
-No, that's not the problem-dasu!
-Hey, Musashi! At a graveyard around this place...
으악! 듣고 싶지 않소!
Ahhh! I don't want to listen-dasu!
무사시의 마음을 어지럽힌 적의 공격은 갔다. 점점 치열해지는 한조의 마의 손에... 가라, 가라, 무사시!
The enemy's attack that deluded Musashi is no more. Now, to the intense evil hands of Hanzō... Go, go, Musashi!
지지 마라, 무사시! 질풍노도의 여행을 계속해라!
Do not lose, Musashi! Keep going on with your stormy journey!
カラのポケットに　ツキが
飛び込むことも　あるさ
おっきな声で　笑えば
あしたには　朝が来る
無くすものなんか　何もないさ
やっちゃえ！イケイケ！
手ぶらは　強いぜ
てなもんだ　のーてんきに行こう
人生　てなもんさ　チャンスが　ほら
しっぽを振って　追ってくるぜ
てなもんだ　のーてんきに行こう
未来も　てなもんさ　あしたが　ほら
両手ひろげて　笑ってるぜ
겨울은 사내의 로망이오. 하고 점잔 뺄 때가 아니오.
Winter is the ideal of men-dasu. And it is not the time to act like a gentleman-dasu.
나, 뱃멀미로 기분이 안 좋소.
I don't feel so good because of seasickness-dasu.
엎친 데 덮친 격으로 이번엔 카라쿠리 상어를 쓰는 해적, 오니고로시가 나타났소.
Misfortune comes after another; this time, Onigoroshi, who uses a karakuri shark, has appeared-dasu.
다이스케하고 손을 잡아, 우리는 한번 운송선에 타게 되었소.
With Daisuke, we rode on a transportation ship-dasu.
다음 이야기! 바다는 무섭네, 오니고로시이오
Next story! The Sea is Scary - It's Onigoroshi!
질풍노도의 복수이오!
It's time for a stormy revenge-dasu!
다음 이야기
바다는 무섭네
오니고로시이오
기대하세요!
Next Episode
The Sea is Scary
It's Onigoroshi
Look forwards for it!